# TRUONG HOANG QUOC DUY

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER



## **ABOUT ME**

With a big interest in Software Development, I have taken 5 projects during University and had hands-on experience in Web Development.

In the next three years, I want to be a Senior Full-stack Software Engineer. I am a software engineer and have a knowledge of English.

I'm confident that I am different:

- Eager to learn The more you learn, the more useful it is
- · Courageous and not afraid to fail.
- · Strong creative and analytical skills.

Birthday: Nov 22nd, 2000

#### CONTACT

Phone: (+84) 793 960 152

Website: My site

Email: truongduy.fu@gmail.com

Github: @duytruong23
Linkedin: @duytruong23

Addr: Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City

### **EDUCATION**

# HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

2018 - Present

# Bachelor of Information Technology, Major in Software Engineer

• English: Low Intermediate

• GPA: 2.70/4.0

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: Html/Css, Javascript, Php.

Framework: VueJS, Laravel, NuxtJS, Bootstrap.

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

For Work: Multi Tasks, Teamwork.

For Personal: Try Hard, Research, Agility, Time

Management.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **VIET JAPAN PARTNER**

From 8/2021 - 02/2022

• Role: Intern Front-end Developer

Language: Html/Css, Javascript, C#, Php.
Framework: NuxtJS, Laravel, .Net Core 5.

• Database: Microsoft SQL, MySQL.

• Methodology: Agile, Waterfall.

Interface development 5 projects. Convert figma to html/css based on customer request.

# HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

From 5/2021 - 7/2021

#### **Shoe Box - Ecommerce**

Course project

· Role: Fullstack Developer

• Team size: 3 members

• Language: C#, Html/Css

• Database: Microsoft SQL

### **EXPECTED POSITION**

· Master Front-end Developer

• BrSE (Bridge Software Engineer)